http://www.albinapipebending.com/privacy-policy

BENDING PROFILES
ANGLEBULB FLATBARBEAMS / WIDE FLANGECHANNELPLATERAILPIPE & TUBESQUARE & RECTANGULAR TUBE (HSS)TEE
SPECIALTY BENDING
SPIRAL BENDSMULTI-AXIS AND MULTI-PLANE BENDINGOFF-AXIS BENDINGVARIABLE-RADIUS BENDSREVERSE-COMPOUND BENDS
BENDING METHODS
INDUCTION BENDINGROTARY DRAW / COMPRESSION BENDINGROLLING / PYRAMID ROLLINGPLATE ROLLINGPOINT BENDING / GAG PRESSINGSYNCHRONIZED INCREMENTAL COLD BENDINGHOT BENDINGCAPACITIES CHARTCUSTOM FABRICATION
DUCT COMPONENTS
ANGLE RINGSPLATE FLANGESCUTOFFSELBOWSCLAMP TOGETHER DUCTINGOTHER COMPONENT PARTSCALCULATORS
BENDING CALCULATORSSPIRAL MATH CALCULATORTANGENT MATERIALSBENDING TOLERANCESCONVERSION CHARTS, WEIGHTS & DIMENSIONSWORK EXAMPLES
ARCHITECTURAL & STRUCTURALSPIRAL STRINGERS & STAIRSOEM & INDUSTRIAL PARTSWHY CURVED STEEL
DESIGN GUIDEFACTS ABOUT CURVED STEELBROCHURESTECHNICAL ARTICLESDETAILINGGLOSSARY OF TERMSINDUSTRY LINKSQUOTE REQUEST
RFQ FOR BENDING & FABRICATIONRFQ FOR DUCT SYSTEMS & COMPONENT PARTSINFO REQUIRED FOR AN ORDER
CURVED STEEL
Your Bending Experts
WHY USE CURVED STEEL?
Reduce Risk & Control Cost
USE CURVED STEEL
It's Recyclable & Looks Great
FAMILY OWNED &AMP OPERATED
Since 1939
YOUR TRUSTED ADVISERS
We Value Our Relationships
AWARD-WINNING PROJECTS
VALUE ADDED SERVICES
Custom Fabrication!
HOME > PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
How do we protect visitor information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order, enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled it won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
Remarketing with Google AdSense
Google Display Network Impression Reporting
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information:
• By emailing us
• By calling us
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users (account users with secure login only) via email
In most timely manner possible
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.albinaco.com
12080 SW Myslony St.
Tualatin, Oregon 97062
United States
info@albinaco.com
Last Edited on 2016-03-11
Your Steel Bending Experts
People Like Us!
I was talking to a potential customer yesterday about fabrication of some complicated work, most of which included rolling. When asked about maintaining tolerances, I could say without hesitation that Albina would provide a product that exceeded expectations. It's good to know you have a partner that can carry their weight when bidding tough projects.
Drew P.
Come Inside
Curved steel members don't just "come that way" from the mill. Curved steel members are produced from straight lengths of material and are bent per your specifications.
Albina Co., Inc. produces the highest quality curved steel products in the steel industry and provides the most reliable and professional
customer service experience.
Latest Posts
What’s Cool In Steel?: December Issue of Modern Steel Features Barbara Walker Crossing Footbridge
8:43 PM, December 03, 2020
“Daunting Curves Ahead”- Article in O & M Metal Fabricator
10:23 PM, November 18, 2020
Signature Spiral Staircase at the Buddy Holly Hall of Arts & Sciences
Toll Free: 866-ALBINA8 (252-4628)
Email: info@albinaco.com
2020 © All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy
